好了  伙计们
Okay, gang.
今晚  录影带告别仪式继续
Tonight, the Farewell to VHS Festival continues.
大寒潮[《山水又相逢》]以来  这里变得很冷
It's been mighty cold in here since "The Big Chill."
能够温暖我们内心的就是
What say we warm our hearts by...
圣艾尔摩之火[电影《七个毕业生》]
"St. Elmo's Fire"?
没错
Yes!
一边喝清爽酒  一边看80年代帅哥
Couple of wine coolers and some '80s Rob Lowe--
我应该会喜欢
I can get into that.
我还是希望今晚有我自己的计划
I'm still holding out hope I'll have plans tonight.
太好了  两个都赞同  海莉呢
Great. Two for two. Haley?
听起来很有意思  但我没空参加
Oh, so fun, but I'm gonna have to say no.
我有个摄影课的事情
I have a photography-class thing.
什么事情
What kind of a thing?
就是展览嘛
Oh, you know, just an exhibit,
展示我们的照片什么的
like, to show our photos.
需要我们参加吗
Is it something that we should go to?
克莱尔  我们有计划了
Claire, we just made plans.
老妈  这是大学的课程
Mom, this is a college class.
我不是三年级小学生了
I'm not in the third grade.
你们不是还有午休时间么
Don't you have nap time there?
没有  我只有空课时间
No. I have free periods,
那时候我才偶尔午休一下
during which I sometimes nap.
是我想多了 还是她刚刚故意说得很含糊
Is it me, or was she just being purposefully vague?
艾丽克斯  你去看看她的东西
Alex, I want you to go through her stuff
查出她今晚到底是干嘛
and find out about this thing tonight.
等等
Wait, wait.
我觉得我们这样窥探不太好
I-I don't feel good about us snooping.
我知道  所以我才让艾丽克斯去做
I know. That's why I told Alex to do it.
我觉得海莉知道的比看上去的多
I think Haley knows more than she's letting on.
你这样想真是伤透了我的心
It breaks my heart how badly you want to believe that.
我们过会儿见
We'll see you guys later.
你们要去哪里
Where are you going?
骑自行车去赞德家
Riding our bikes to Xander's.
你们去那里干什么
What are you doing there?
不知道啊  就一起玩玩
I don't know. Hanging out.
听起来很有意思  戴上头盔哦
Sounds fun. Wear your helmets.
会的
We will.
我可不想插着呼吸机写我的第一本小说
I'm not writing my first novel by blowing through a tube.
我不喜欢他们去那孩子家
I don't like them going over to that kid's house.
为什么
Why not?
赞德会带坏他们的
Mm, Xander's a bad influence.
他哥哥简直更糟糕
His older brother is even worse.
满身肌肉的大块头  很爱抽大麻
Huge stoner always walking around
总穿着他的军装瞎晃悠
in his army jacket with his muscles,
还老喜欢拨弄头发  露出蓝眼睛
flipping his hair out of his blue eyes.
他有一次还说我漂亮
He told me I was looking good one time.
拜托省省吧
I mean, come on.
好吧  我们会留意的
Yeah, we'll keep our eye on that.
但现在问题是赞德  我不信任他
But for now...Xander. I don't trust him.
克莱尔  你真是难以捉摸
Claire, you're a tough one to figure out.
你不信任坏男孩  却嫁给了我
You don't trust bad boys, and yet you married one.
■
m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0
m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35
m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60
m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172
本字幕由人人影视字幕组翻译
禁止用作任何商业盈利行为
翻译：小饭  冰蓝  姚小事儿  罂粟无果  小花豆  丁小七
时间轴：浓子   校对：olivia_xuxu   后期&总监：瓜瓜
摩  登
家  庭
第五季 第十四集
我的帅小子饿坏了
My handsome boy's so hungry.
好了  我很快回来
All right. Be back in a few.
如果小短打电话来  告诉他我死了
If Shorty calls, tell him I died,
但要保证让他信服
but make sure you really sell it.
我们在玩一个很有趣的游戏
It's a funny thing we're doing.
那怎么会好玩
How is that funny?
我就知道你会这样说
I knew you'd say that.
总之别接电话  再见  伙计
Just don't answer the phone. Bye, buddy.
这是怎么回事
What's all that about?
你生我气了还是怎么了
You mad at me or something?
我不知道
I don't know.
你有做什么让我生气的事吗
Did you do something to make me mad?
那样的话  我就是在生气
Because then I am.
如果没有  我就没生气
But if you didn't, then I am not.
我什么也没干啊
I didn't do anything.
那我就没生气
Then I am not mad.
我生气了
I am mad.
昨晚  杰做了个有关别的女人的春梦
Last night, Jay had a sexy dream about some woman.
宝贝
Baby.
Oh, baby.
宝贝
Oh, baby!
我知道那不是我
And I know it wasn't about me,
因为他知道我讨厌男人叫我宝贝
Because he knows that I hate when men call me baby.
没错  人们允许有自己的私密想法
And, yes, people are allowed their private thoughts,
我也不应该这么生气
and I shouldn't be so angry,
但我是拉丁人  所以姐想生气就生气
But I am latin, so I get to feel whatever I want.
你想跟我说我干了什么吗
You want to tell me what I did?
你想跟我说你干了什么吗
Do you want to tell me what you did?
我不知道我干了什么啊
I don't know what I did.
那我就不知道你干了什么
Then I don't know what you did.
我受够了  我要走了
I'm bored. I'm going.
别忘了你的手机
Don't forget your phone.
我手臂上有片淤青
I got a bruise on my arm.
不知道从哪儿来的
I don't know where it came from.
可怜的宝贝
Oh, poor baby.
于是我意识到
And then I realized
我不想为查理工作了
I don't want to work for Charlie anymore.
我真正想要的是
What I really want --
抱歉  我听不下去了
I'm sorry. I can't listen to this.
我要跟你说件事
I need to tell you something,
但你得保密
but you have to keep it a secret.
当然  我是律师
Of course. I'm a lawyer.
我还听过谋杀供述呢
I've heard murder confessions.
-真的吗  -好吧  在
- Really?   - Well, in --
在法学院的模拟法庭上
in mock trials at law school.
不过我还是守口如瓶
But still, I never told anyone.
说真的  只跟你说
Seriously, this is only for you.
连小卡都不能说  你能保证吗
You can't even tell Cam. Promise?
好
Uh, okay.
你还好吗
Is everything all right?
看桌子下面
Look under the table.
脚踝以上  膝盖以下  你看到什么了
Above the ankle, below the knee, what do you see?
我对此有点紧张  但是
I'm a little nervous about this, but --
天啊  你没有吧
Oh, oh, my gosh! You didn't?
我做了  小腿肌肉植入
I did. Calf implants.
你还真是没少往里面植入啊
Wow, and you really went for it, didn't you?
不不不  它们还肿着呢
No, no, no. They're still swollen.
所以你才穿着运动裤
And that's why you're wearing sweat pants.
好吧  我...
Okay, I was --
我还怕你就这样放弃
I was afraid you'd just given up.
真是松了口气
So, whew!
它们会恢复的
They'll settle.
我打算随意地提到我的新健身计划
I'm gonna start casually referencing my new workout plan,
然后在阵亡将士纪念日那天
and then I'm gonna debut them
我会在拉古纳海滩展示出来
memorial day at Laguna beach.
我个人认为你不需要这样
I personally don't think that you needed them,
但如果那能让你开心
but if they make you happy --
-会的  -那就好
- They do. - Good.
我总是想成为
I always wanted to be
穿着紧身裤跑步的男人
one of those guys running in tights,
但我的小腿腿型还不够完美
but I was too embarrassed about my legs.
如果你去跑步...
Well, if you'd just gone running --
你多虑了  米奇尔
Yep. You're overthinking this, Mitchell.
不开玩笑  你不能告诉小卡
No joke, you can't tell Cam.
我爱他  但他是个超级大嘴巴
I love him, but he is a giant blabbermouth.
拜托  他没那么坏啦
Oh, come on. He's not that bad.
他只是  算了  我自己都不信
He just -- yeah, no, I can't even sell that.
杰  哪阵风把你吹来寒舍了
Jay, to what do I owe the pleasure?
我只是来接曼尼的
I'm just here to pick up Manny.
没必要搞这么隆重
No need for a whole thing.
我不知道我为什么要那样对他
I don't know why I do that to him.
他见到我总是很高兴
The guy's always so happy to see me.
我懒得管了
I'm not gonna worry about it.
曼尼不在
Manny's not here.
他和卢克去了赞德家
He actually went with Luke over to Xander's.
曼尼也没告诉你他要去那里吗
Whoa! Manny didn't tell you he was going either?
我告诉过你  那些男孩子在隐瞒什么
I told you, those boys are being cagey.
有可能是
There is a chance
歌洛莉亚让我白跑一趟来惩罚我
Gloria let me drive over here for nothing as punishment.
我觉得她偷看了我的手机
I think she snooped on my phone,
读了几封邮件
read some of my e-mails.
这样可不好  邮件是个人隐私
That's not cool. E-mails are private.
是找我借钱的朋友发来的
They were from a friend I loaned money to.
-绝对是你的特权  -一个女人
- 100% your prerogative. - A woman.
不是吧
Oh, no.
我来告诉你我会怎么做
Well, I'll tell you what I'd do.
我会告诉我女人
I'd tell my lady,
你没权力干涉我的事
"You got no business being in my business."
尊重你男人的隐私
Respect your man's boundaries.
亲爱的  你答应过
Honey, you promised
做完布朗尼蛋糕后会洗盘子的
you'd clean the pan if you made brownies.
也许我忘了先喷点水
Well, maybe I forgot to spray it first
现在我让它泡着呢  女人
and I'm letting it soak, woman.
你来时他才这样说话
He only talks like this when you're around.
那他今天可以到此为止了
Well, then, he's done for the day.
好吧  很好
Oh, okay. Good.
-拜拜  爸  -回头见  伙计
- Bye, dad. - See ya...buddy.
我追踪了卢克的手机
I have tracked Luke's cellphone,
他可不在赞德家附近
and he is nowhere near his friend Xander's.
亲爱的  我像下一位沃兹尼克一样热爱科技
Honey, I love technology as much as the next Wozniak,
[苹果公司创始人]
但我们真的要监视自家孩子吗
but are we sure we want to be spying on our kids?
不要  你也不该用伪造的身份
No, and you also shouldn't try to friend us
在Facebook上加我们好友
with fake Facebook profiles,
玛戈特・拉克鲁瓦
Margot LaCroix.
我原本期望
I was really hoping some
你工作以后能不这么疯狂了呢
of this would go away when you got a job.
我直接问他怎么样
How about I just ask him?
天啊
Oh, man.
真希望你是我爸爸
I wish you were my dad.
能避免我犯多少我没犯过的错啊
The things I would have done.
-喂  -儿子
- Hello? - Hey, buddy.
只是想确定你平安到达了赞德家
Just making sure you got to Xander's okay.
是啊  平安无事
Yep. All good.
真的吗  因为我听到汽车的声音
Really? 'cause I hear traffic...
赞德住在一条很安静的街道上  对吧
...and Xander lives on a pretty quiet street, right?
其实我们离开了赞德家
Actually, we left Xander's,
现在我们在萨米这里
and now we're at Sammy's.
这就讲得通了
Well, that makes perfect sense.
你好好玩  注意安全
You have fun. Be safe.
他在撒谎
He's lying.
瞧  他朋友萨米住在这里
Look. His friend Sammy lives here.
而他在奥林匹克街和20号大街的路口
He's all the way over on Olympic and 20th.
奥林匹克街和20号大街吗
Olympic and 20th?
那是一家废品回收站
That's the old salvage yard
孩子们会去那里嗑药
where kids go to get high.
-什么  -不
- What?! - No.
我们现在就要赶过去
Oh, we are going there right now.
等等  你确定吗
Wait, wait, wait. Are you sure?
我回答完这个问题后就出门
I'm gonna answer, and then I'm gonna walk away.
好吗
Deal?
好
Okay.
我百分之420肯定
I'm 420% sure.
她数学真差
Wow, she's bad at math.
爱人们
Hey, guys.
二爸
Hi, daddy.
午饭怎么样
How was lunch?
还不错
Oh, it was fine.
人们什么时候开始往沙拉里加三文鱼了
Hey, when did salmon become a thing that we put on salad?
市里是2008年  郊区是2011年
2008 in the city, 2011 in the suburbs.
布雷特怎么样  今天又有什么好戏
How was Brett? What's the drama du jour?
没什么
Nothing.
拜托  他就不是个安分的角色
Oh, please. It's never nothing with that one.
他的烫发  假装自己有跟踪者
His perm, the stalker he pretends to have,
在国税局工作就没人愿意和你约会了
nobody will date you when you work at the I.R.S.
我烦死了  这次又是什么事
I hate it. What was it this time?
说真的  没事
No, seriously, nothing.
也许在沙拉里加点鸡肉以外的东西
I guess it is nice to have something other than chicken
也挺好的
to throw on there.
你为什么逃避话题
Okay, why are you being so evasive?
我没有逃避啊  我...
I'm not being evasive. I--
瞧瞧这条新领带
Check out this new tie.
我的天
Oh, my gosh.
你在转移话题
You are redirecting me,
就像我们不想回答
like we do when Lily asks us a question
莉莉的问题时
we don't want to answer
就把娃娃塞到她面前
and just throw a doll in her face.
等等
Wait a minute.
别胡思乱想了
Don't be ridiculous.
我怎么会这么糊弄一个成年人
Like I could do that with an adult.
看看我给你买了什么
Check out what I got for you.
太好了  压蒜器
Oh, good, yes. A garlic press.
我还真受不了我的手指闻起来
I am so tired of my fingers smell--
我的天  你又在转移话题了
Oh, my gosh. You did it again.
-什么  -肯定很劲爆
- What's that? - Oh, it's got to be good.
-什么  -告诉我
- What?!  - Tell me.
-不  没什么  -告诉我
- No, nothing.  - Tell me.
-没什么好说的 -告诉我
- There's nothing to tell!  - Tell me.
-没什么可说的  -告诉我  告诉我
- There's nothing to tell! - Tell me, tell me,
告诉我  告诉我
tell me, tell me.
来  回答我
Here. Answer me.
圣诞老人怎么去得了那么多房子
How does santa claus get to all of those houses?
好了亲爱的  大人在说话呢
Okay, sweetie, the adults are talking right now,
看爸爸给你买了什么
And look what daddy brought you.
米奇尔  要是有人跟我说了什么
Mitchell, when somebody tells me something,
我都等不及回家告诉你
I can't wait to get home and tell you.
你难道没有同感吗
Don't you feel the same?
我当然有了
Of course I do.
但是他  他让我保证不说的
But he -- he made me promise.
你知道吗  我们不需要分享秘密
Well, you know what? We don't have to share secrets.
不需要
We don't.
我们都已经分享了房子  生活
We already share a house, a life,
还有个女儿
a daughter.
你知道吗  我不
You know what?I don't --
我不知道我为什么这么在意
I don't know why I care so much.
好吧  好吧
Okay, all right, okay.
他做了小腿肌肉植入
He got calf implants.
我的上帝  什么效果啊
Oh, my god! Oh, what do they look like?
就像他偷运了两个葡萄柚一样
Like he's smuggling two grapefruits.
而且我的沙拉里也有葡萄柚
Which, by the way, were also on my salad.
这可是大新闻啊  太大了
Okay, this is huge. This is huge.
都谁知道  我们得请他们来吃早午餐
Who all knows? We have to host a brunch.
不许跟任何人说  知道吗
Don't you dare tell a single person, okay?
他让我保证不告诉别人 特别是你
He made me promise not to tell anyone, especially you.
-特别是我  -拜托
- Especially me?   - Oh, please.
谁都知道你守不住秘密
Everybody knows you're terrible at keeping secrets.
好吧 我还不知道我有这样的名声
Okay, well, I didn't know that was my reputation.
也许这是个大家都在瞒着我的秘密
Maybe that's a secret people have been keeping from me.
我不想伤害你的感情
I didn't mean to hurt your feelings.
你已经伤了
Well, you did.
你知道让人难过的是什么吗
And you know what the sad thing is?
我们本来可以一起嘲笑某人的小腿植入的
We could be laughing at someone's calf implants right now.
你在干什么
Hey, what are you doing?
我只是在欣赏你的睡姿
I'm just watching you sleep.
你看上去真漂亮
You look so pretty.
好吧  但别太大声喘气
Okay, but don't breathe so loud.
你去哪儿啊
Hey, where are you going?!
我找不到可以进去的地方
I can't find a way in.
我什么都看不见
I can't see anything,
但我听见他们的笑声了
but I hear them laughing.
你知道小孩子为什么会笑
And you know why kids laugh.
因为他们心中充满喜悦  而不是怀疑吗
Because their hearts are filled with joy, not suspicion?
我们一定要搞清楚他们在干什么
We have got to see what is going on in there.
把那个嗡嗡响的东西从车里拿出来
Get the drone thing out of the car.
那个'东西'可是专业航空摄影器材
That "Thing" is a professional aerial-photography tool
只为房地产事业服务
for real-estate use only!
你用它拍你自己在沙滩堆小天使
You used it at the beach to film yourself doing sand angels.
那是我在拍宣传片
For my "Phil Dunphy Will Get You
《菲尔为您的海滨别墅提供天堂般好价格》
a Heavenly Deal On a Beach House" video.
专业房地产用具
A professional real-estate tool!
你答应过了的
That was the consensus.
喂  艾利克斯  你找到什么了
Hey, Alex. What did you find out?
好吧  这件事确实比海莉说的更重大
Okay, this is a bigger deal than Haley let on.
她班上只有5个人
Only five people in her class
被选上参加摄影展
were picked to show their photographs,
海莉是其中之一
And haley was one of them.
太棒了
Amazing!
她班上一共不止5个人吧
Are there more than five people in the class?
是的  那是我最先核查的
Yes. That's the first thing I checked.
那我们确实一定要去看看了
Then we really do have to be there.
打电话邀请米奇尔舅舅和外公一起来
Call uncle Mitchell and grandpa and see if they can join us.
她没发现你打探她的隐私吧
She didn't catch you snooping, did she?
没有  她在睡午觉
No. She's taking a nap.
她最近睡午觉比以前多多了
She's been taking a lot more naps lately.
去看看能不能查出是怎么回事
See what you can find out about that.
这样做太不对了
This is so wrong.
特殊时期特殊...
Eh, well, desperate times call for desperate --
你脑袋上是什么东西
What is on your head?
用来防眩光的  但显然挡不住你的怒视
It provides glare protection, but apparently not from you.
赶紧开始吧
Let's just do this.
我们是空军
We are airborne.
熟练地越过电线
Expertly navigating the wires.
你说得对
You're right.
我们已经通过围墙  接近目标
We have cleared the wall. Approaching target.
他们在那里
There they are.
他们在干什么
What are they doing?
他们在什么东西上跳来跳去
They're jumping around on stuff.
你看到什么可疑的东西了吗  比如
Do you see anything suspicious, like, um --
比如烟或者什么相关设备  干酪玉米片
like smoke or paraphernalia, nachos?
不  他们在互相拍摄
No, they're filming each other
还像僵尸那样跳来跳去
and moving around like zombies.
亲爱的  他们没在吸毒
Honey, they're not getting high.
他们在拍电影  居然没带我
They're making a movie... without me!
等等  等等  等等
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
那为什么卢克要撒谎说
Then why would luke have lied
去萨米家呢
about going to Sammy's, huh?
亲爱的  你看
Honey, look.
萨米废品回收站
天啊
Oh, god.
他还是我们的小乖乖
Well, he's still our little boy.
我们得走了
Oh, we got to get out of here.
可不能让他知道我们监视他
He cannot know we were spying on him.
-快点  -已经晚了
- Come on. - Too late.
太晚了  他们发现了我的遥控飞机
It's too late. They're pointing at the drone.
-什么  -我们被发现了
- What?  - We're compromised!
快走  快走
Get out, get out!
我不能丢下遥控飞机
I can't leave the drone!
那是公司财产
It belongs to the office!
他们还在因为我在白板上
They're still mad at me for writing
用永久性记号笔而生我的气呢
on the dry-erase board with a permanent marker!
快上车
Get in the car.
快走  快走
Go, go, go!
那是什么东西
What was that thing?
有人在偷拍我们
Somebody was filming us.
我爸有个那种玩意儿
Hey, my dad has one of those.
我知道怎么回事了
I know what's going on here.
有个电影公司想偷我们的点子
A movie studio is trying to steal our idea!
斯皮尔伯格
Spielberg.
我就说过  僵尸跑酷是个超棒的点子
I told you guys, zombie parkour is a million-dollar idea.
我还是没懂  僵尸移动速度不够快
I still don't get it. Zombies don't move well.
吸血鬼估计会好一点
Vampires, maybe.
标题我都想好了  "吸血鬼跑酷"
Plus, there's your title -- "Vam-par-kour."
我听不出有什么特别的
I don't hear it.
瞧瞧
Look at that.
我最喜欢回到家被这样迎接了
That's how I like to be greeted when I come home!
曼尼今天跟朋友出去玩了
It turns out Manny's hanging with his friends today,
所以我不用接他
so I didn't need to go pick him up.
是哦  不好意思忘了告诉你
Oh, right. So sorry. I forgot to tell you.
不过  反正你也不是什么都告诉我
But, then, you don't tell me everything,
所以没什么所谓
so I guess it's okay.
你说这话太过分了
You got a lot of nerve.
你都已经查过我手机上的邮件了
You are the one who went through my emails on my phone.
你在说什么  我才没有
What are you talking about? No, I didn't.
所以你不是因为我手机里的东西生气
So you're not mad at me for something you found on my phone?
不是
No.
好吧  那很好
All right, then. Great.
没有伤害就不算犯规
No harm, no foul.
晚餐见
I'll see you at dinner.
把手机给我
Give me that phone!
我要看看你在藏什么
I want to see what you're hiding!
我什么都没有藏
I'm not hiding anything.
我都不知道怎么用这该死的玩意儿
I don't even know how to use the damn thing.
看吧  我不小心拨给了艾丽克斯
Oh, look. I accidentally dialed Alex.
我先跟她说两句  她可崇拜我了
Let me say hi to her. The kid idolizes me.
你好  宝贝
Hi, hon.
外公好
Hi, Grandpa.
问个问题  我要怎么删除手机上的邮件
Real quick, how do I delete e-mails on my phone?
你得先查一下收件箱
Well, first, you have to check your inbox,
垃圾箱还有已发送邮件
your trash folder, and your sent folder.
很多人会忽略已发送邮件
People often forget about the sent folder.
相信我  你要是也得抢在一个
Trust me, you get pretty adept at this
喜欢偷窥的老妈之前删掉邮件
when you have to stay one step
你也会很擅长这个的
ahead of your snooping mother.
把电话给我
Give me the phone.
我得挂了
Got to go.
好的  我  我手机里没有秘密
Uh, yeah, sure. I-I-I have nothing on here.
我先挂了外公的电话
Let me just disconnect from grandpa,
好像挂不掉
which is not happening right now.
我看到你在干什么了  艾丽克斯
I can see what you're doing, Alex.
你干嘛要删掉米奇尔舅舅的短信
Why did just delete a text from uncle Mitchell?
我没有
I didn't!
你不是应该更担心
Shouldn't you be more worried
海莉衣柜里的护士服吗
that Haley has a nurse's uniform in her closet?!
我一次只能顾得上一件事
I can only handle one thing at a time.
-你好  克莱尔  -你好  米奇尔
- Hey, Claire. - Hey, Mitchell.
为什么艾丽克斯要删掉你给她的短信
Why would Alex delete a text from you off her phone?
这个问题我不回答
I'm not answering that question.
手机是人家的私事
People's phones are their own business.
怎么了
What?
我得挂了  把手机给我
I got to go. Give me your phone.
不行  凭什么
No. Why?
因为你在跟人发短信
Because you're texting someone
而且看起来很内疚
and you look very guilty right now.
我在玩"一起来填词"
Or I'm playing "Words with friends"
跟朗吉尼斯一起
with Longines.
猜的词包括"小腿肌肉"和"植入"吧
None of those words better be "Calf" or "Implants."
天啊  给你  你知道吗
Oh, my gosh. Here. You know what?
拿走我的手机
Take my phone...
然后承认你一点都不信任我吧
and admit that you don't trust me,
你的未婚夫  和你女儿的另一个爹
Your fiance, and co-father of your daughter.
查吧
Go ahead.
按键啊
Push the button.
没什么  我很好  我信任你
I'm good. No, I'm fine. I trust you.
我的天啊
Oh, my gosh!
伙计们
Hey, guys.
想喝点红色的像酒的东西吗
You want some red stuff that reminds you of wine?
-当然  -我也是
- Sure. - Yep, I do.
展会什么时候开
So, when's this exhibit open?
我不知道  细节大概还在杰的手机里
I don't know. Maybe the details are in Jay's phone.
不过我希望不是
But I hope not,
毕竟那里面装的都是秘密
because everything is very secret on there.
你们大概也看出来了
Don't know if you caught that subtle cue.
她在生我的气
She's mad at me.
他做了很可怕的事
He did something very terrible
又不愿意让我知道
that he doesn't want me to know about.
很可怕
"Very terrible"?
除非你告诉我
Until you tell me what it is,
不然我会联想到最坏的可能
I'm gonna think the worst possible thing,
比如你杀了个人
like maybe you killed somebody.
不过你估计没那个能耐  是吧
But you don't have the stomach for that, do you?
真高兴你们能来
Thank you so much for coming.
我知道你们都忙着工作和杂事
I know how busy you all are with work and errands
还有卑鄙地在短信里说我闲话
and snarking about me on your cellphone.
别纠结这事了  克莱尔
Let it go, Claire.
说实话  菲尔  我不知道你是怎么忍受的
Honestly, Phil, i don't know how you do it.
我不知道你是怎么忍受的
I don't know how you do it.
退一步海阔天空
Compromise and compassion.
她不是真的在问你
She wasn't really asking you.
卢克来了
Hey, hey! Here comes Luke.
我们该说我们今天干了什么
What do we say we were doing today?
什么时候卢克关心过我们干了什么
When has Luke ever showed any interest in what we do?
好吧  放轻松
Okay, but be cool.
如果他发现你追踪了他的手机
If he finds out you were tracking his phone,
他会认为我们不信任他
he'll think we don't trust him.
可不是  而且我也就不能继续追踪了
Ooh. Plus, then I could never do it again.
你们好啊
Hey, guys!
你好
What's up?
你今天过得怎么样
How was your day?
还不错  你们知道的
It was fine, you know.
我们不知道  我们怎么会知道
We don't know. How would we know?
我们只是问问而已
Oh, we just mean what did you do?
不是在问你都做了些什么
Not like, what did you do?
只是顺口一问"嗨  你都做了些什么"
And we're just like, "Hey, what -- what'd you do?"
你们表现得好奇怪
You guys are acting weird.
我们没有  你才奇怪
No, we're not. You are.
你们今天都做了些什么
What did you do today?
-我们只是待在家里  -我们去购物了
- We just stayed home  - We went shopping.
在家里网购裤子
Online shopping at home for pants.
我们俩都需要裤子
We both needed pants.
我跟你说过了他会问起的
I told you he was gonna ask.
等一下
Wait a minute.
今天那是你的遥控飞机吗
Was that your drone today?
你们在暗中监视我们吗
Were you spying on us?
对不起  是你妈妈逼我做的
I'm sorry. Your mom made me do it.
她以为你在吸大麻
She thought you were smoking grass.
大麻  克莱尔
Grass? Claire.
现在没人用大麻这个词了
No one says grass.
我没说过是大麻
I never said grass.
这种想法也不是那么疯狂
It's not that crazy an idea.
我们什么都没有吸
We weren't smoking anything.
曼尼永远不会做那种事
Manny would never.
谢谢  妈妈
Thank you, mom.
他总是很嫌弃那种事情
He's so judgy about those things.
我遛那条蠢狗的唯一原因
The only reason why I walk that stupid dog
就是我可以安静的抽会儿烟
is so that I can smoke my cigars in peace.
我简直不敢相信你监视我们
I can't believe you were spying on us.
你不能再这么疑神疑鬼的了  克莱尔
You have to stop being so suspicious, Claire.
你要学会相信别人
It's okay to trust people.
某些人可以  其他人  鬼知道
Some people. Other people, who knows?
你就疏忽了一秒钟
You turn your back for one second,
他们就不知在什么鬼地方
and they have a whole other family
组建了一个新家庭
on the bad side of town.
你就是我组建的新家庭
You are my other family from the bad side of town.
我不能一晚上都得忍受这些指责
Look, I can't stand this all night.
我借钱给别人了  歌洛莉亚
I loaned someone money, Gloria.
我没有征求你的意见因为我知道你会生气
I didn't consult you. I knew you'd be pissed.
她只是一个朋友
She's just a friend.
"她"
"She"?
这就是那个
Is this the woman
你夜里梦见的女人吗
that you've been dreaming about at night,
你甚至用性感的嗓音叫她
that you've been making the sexy noises and saying,
"宝贝  宝贝"
"Baby, baby"?
你这是在说些什么  当然不是
What the hell are you talking about?! No?!
那就证明一下  给我你的手机
Then prove it! Give me the phone!
实话说  你们这群人
Honestly, you people --
我指的是你们这些直人  简直太可笑了
and by that, I mean straight people are ridiculous!
每个人都有权力拥有一些隐私
Everyone's entitled to a little bit of privacy.
逼我说出朋友的秘密的人
Says the guy who forced me to
还好意思说出这种话
tell him our friend's secret.
好吧  那是不一样的
Okay, that's different.
那是八卦
That was gossip,
-八卦是属于所有人的  -好吧
- and gossip belongs to everyone.  - Okay.
别老惦记着别人的手机了
Just keep your nose out of other people's phones.
你要么就相信他们要么就不
You either trust them or you don't.
把手机给我
Give me that.
-终于拿到了  -还给我  还给
- Ha! Yes.  - Give it back. Give it --
不行  但你可以拿我的看
No, but you can have mine,
因为我光明磊落
'cause I have nothing to hide.
我要了
I'll take that.
天哪  妈妈  不要这样做
Oh, my god. Mom, no, please, stop.
在这  在这  等等  我帮你拿出来
Here, here. Wait. Let me help you.
这太疯狂了  对吧
It's crazy, right?
我就知道
Ha ha. No, I knew it.
笑死了
"L.O.L.
你觉得布雷特喜欢喝黑咖啡
Do you think Brett likes his coffee black
还是一半咖啡一半水
or with calf-and-calf?"
[calf小腿与half一半 音似]
好吧  我承认  我是有问题
Okay, I admit it. I have a problem.
但我只告诉了一个人  这消息太劲爆了
But I only told one person. It was too juicy.
而且克里斯宾说了他会保守秘密
And Crispin said he wouldn't tell anyone.
这条是朗吉尼斯发来的
This is from Longines.
那个骗子克里斯宾  把手机还给我
Oh, that lying Crispin. Give me that.
我不敢相信他背叛了我的信任
I cannot believe he betrayed my trust.
现在胡娇也插进来了
Now Pepper's chiming in.
大骗子  所有人
Jackals, all of them.
胡娇真会说笑
Oh, that Pepper.
我的天
Oh, my g--
你让米奇尔叔叔帮你给我买生日礼物吗
Uncle Mitchell was helping you get me a birthday present?
是的  我想给你做饭
Yeah, I wanted to make you dinner
然后送你一瓶上好的红酒
and get you a nice bottle of wine,
那瓶他在新年夜给我们喝的
The one he served at new year's
你说你很喜欢
you said you liked.
我确实喜欢那瓶红酒
Ooh, I did like that wine.
我很抱歉我把惊喜给毁了
I'm sorry I ruined the surprise.
你应该觉得抱歉
You should be.
要不然你以为我在干什么
What did you think I was doing, anyways?
你应该信任我才对
Give me some credit.
或许我们可以算是扯平了
Oh, well, then, maybe we could just call it even,
因为他说  我只是很吃惊
since he typed, "I'm just surprised
她还记得那天晚上来过我家
She remembered coming to my house that night."
你回复说  啊哈哈哈
To which you responded, "Bahahahahahaha"
后面还有五个感叹号
with like five exclamation points.
很公平
Seems fair.
找到你要找的东西了吗
Did you find what you were looking for?
没有
No.
她是俱乐部的服务员
She's a waitress at the club.
她的车被男朋友砸了  所以我帮了她
Her boyfriend crashed her car, so I helped her,
因为我们之间有个有趣的游戏
because we have that fun game where I order salad
每次我点沙拉她都给我上薯条
and she brings me french fries.
但是我从来没梦见过她
But I never dreamt of her.
昨天晚上我做了个噩梦
Last night, I had a nightmare.
乔爬到一栋高楼的天台上
Joe got out onto a ledge of a tall building.
我救不到他
I couldn't get to him.
我特别着急
I was very upset,
我可能在梦里还哭了
and I think I might have cried a little in my sleep,
你可能觉得那听起来很色情
which might have sounded like sex to you,
这点我很不喜欢
which I don't love.
但乔才是我喊的那个"宝贝"
But that's the "Baby" I was talking about.
真的吗
Really?
很吓人
That's scary.
是啊
Yes!
苍天在上
Why in god's name
我怎么会梦到别的女人
would I need to dream about another woman?
你这么一说
Now that you say it out loud,
我也觉得的确很离谱
it does seem kind of crazy.
不骄傲地说  我并没有梦到乔
I'm not proud of this, but the dream wasn't about Joe.
而是这个小宝贝
It was about this little baby right here.
没错
That's right.
你差点从天台上掉下去  吓死爸爸了
You almost fell off a ledge, and daddy was so scared.
我的天  是我们
Oh, my gosh. It's us!
全都是
All over the place.
我不知道现在是什么感觉
I don't know how I feel about this.
你看  你有多喜欢八卦
Okay, okay, now, see -- look how much you gossip.
海莉都用胶片捕捉到了
Haley managed to capture it on film.
再看看你  笑得见牙不见眼
And look at you, smiling ear to ear.
你知道你最爱听我说八卦了
You know you love it when I give you the dirt.
这倒是提醒我了
Oh, which reminds me,
猜猜谁刚因为向服务生乱献殷勤
guess who got kicked out of a hotel bar
被赶出大堂酒吧了
for making unwanted advances at the waitstaff?
我不想知道  那不关我的事
I don't want to know. It's none of my business.
好吧
Okay.
约坦  赞尼尔  还是萨尔
Jotham. Zaniel. Sal.
告诉我吧
Just tell me!
我不知道
I don't know.
老天  看看我脸上的皱纹
Good god, look at those lines on my face.
我什么时候变得这么老了
When did I get so old?
那是笑纹  因为你正抱着你的儿子
Their smile lines because you're holding your son
你爱他  在睡梦中都要保护他
who you love, who you had to protect in your dream.
她是个很棒的摄影师
She is a great photographer,
虽然每个人都盯着我的
even though it's embarrassing
六块腹肌  让我很不好意思
that everyone's staring at my six-pack.
她真的很棒
She is really good.
你看到我的照片了吗
Have you seen my photo?
歌洛莉亚看到了吗
Has Gloria seen this?
歌洛莉亚看到什么
Gloria see what?
我觉得我看起来不错
I think I look good.
她都没看到照片里也有我
Wow. She didn't even see me in there.
天啊  你们来干什么
Oh, my god! What are you guys doing here?!
艾丽克斯邀请我们来的
Alex invited us.
你  你怎么知道是在这里的
You? How did you know where this was?
传单从你的背包里掉出来了
Uh, the flier fell out of your backpack.
骗人
Liar.
妈妈逼我的
Mom made me.
我们是来支持你的
We came to be supportive.
我告诉你们不要来的  这太不尊重人了
I told you not to come here. This is such a violation!
她也对我这样
She just did it to me, too.
她看了我的短信
She read my texts.
那没什么
That's nothing.
她用了个遥控飞机监视我
She totally used a drone to spy on me.
我有正当理由使用遥控飞机
Use of the drone was completely justified.
-你有病吗  -你在说什么
- What is wrong with you?! - What are you talking about?
行了  别吵了
All right, knock it off.
你们根本不知道做家长有多难
You have no idea how hard it is to be a parent,
要费尽心思打探孩子们的状况
to figure out what's going on with your kid
你们只会咕哝或者说"还行"
when all you get is a grunt or a "Fine"
或者甩甩头发
or a flick of the hair.
保护你们是我的责任
It's my job to protect you
要保证你们做的选择是对的
and make sure you're making good choices.
如果我在这样做的时候
And if I step over the line every now and again
偶尔有点过分  难免
when I'm doing that, tough.
只有知道你们平安
Knowing you're safe is the only thing
我晚上才能睡着
that lets me sleep at night.
我还以为是靠酒精
I thought it was the wine.
恭喜你  海莉
Congratulations, Haley.
恭喜什么
For what?
有人刚刚买下了你拍的那张
Someone just bought your photo
这位美女的照片
of this beautiful lady.
今天卖出的第一张
First one sold.
天啊
Oh, my god!
有人花钱买了我的作品  我的
Someone paid for something that I made! Me!
我真高兴大家能在这里一起见证
I am so psyched we were here for this!
我也是
Me too!
你现在高兴我们来了吗
Now you're glad we're here, huh?
我必须承认
I got to admit,
你这张照片美极了
that's a gorgeous picture of you.
里面也有我  爸
I'm in it, too, dad.